shopybids.com 2013-04-24

# ShopyBids, The Best Penny Auction Site!- Shopybids.com

#### INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY

ShopyBids.com ("ShopyBids LLC.," "Us," or "We") respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. The following Privacy Policy outlines the information ShopyBids may collect and how we may use that information.

Shopybids.com (hereinafter referred to as “Shopybids”) is a service provided by Shopybids Inc. (hereinafter referred to as “Shopybids” or “We”). We recognize and respect your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all aspects relating to gathering information while you are visiting the Shopybids website, how We handle your personal information for our services and all further permissible uses of such information.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective 10 days after being posted on the website.

#### Data Collection

You may visit Shopybids at any time without providing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, when you visit our website, We may collect and store your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Shopybids, ad data, IP address and standard web log information and information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data.

For you to actively participate in Shopybids, We do need some of your personal information, however. Once you provide us with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers.

In connection with your registration and use of Shopybids, We may collect and store the following personal information:

• email address, physical contact and personal information including but not limited to your name, address, date of birth and telephone number;  
• all transactional information based on your activities on Shopybids;  
• shipping, billing and other information relating to any purchase or shipping;  
• any correspondence sent to us or by us;  
• financial information, such as your credit card information; and  
• other supplemental information from third parties.

#### Use of Data 

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that We and affiliates or members of our corporate group may use your personal information to:

• provide the services and customer support you request;  
• resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;  
• prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions;  
• customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;  
• inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers;  
• contact you for market research; and  
• compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties.

#### Disclosure of Personal Data

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. 

We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should We plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, We will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when We believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

#### Your Information on Shopybids

Once you have been approved as a registered user with Shopybids, you will be required to choose a user name. This user name will be displayed throughout Shopybids and therefore provided to the public. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, users will not be able to personally identify your activities on Shopybids.

#### Access, Review and Change of Personal Data

You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to Shopybids at any time. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or information is inaccurate. 

#### Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account

Upon your request, We will close your account as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our General Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law

You can delete or deactivate your Shopybids account at any time. When you delete your membership, your personal data is removed from our database unless We are required to save the data. 

#### The Use of Cookies at our Website

Shopybids uses so-called “cookies”, which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of “pop-up” windows. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, We would like to point out that turning off these settings may reduce the quality of your experience. 

#### DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy or as specifically agreed to by you, we will not disclose any Personal Information gathered from you on our Website. We may release Personal Information to third parties: (1) to allow our third party partners to offer their products and services to you (2) to comply with valid legal requirements such as a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (3) in special cases, such as a physical threat to you or others.

Disclosure to Operations and Maintenance Contractors

Our operations and maintenance contractors sometimes have limited access to your Personal Information in the course of providing products or services to us. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us with technology, services, and/or content related to better operation and maintenance of our Website. These contractors also may have access to your email address to send newsletters or special promotions to you on our behalf or to send emails to you for purposes such as conducting market research on our behalf. Access to your Personal Information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary in order for the contractor to perform its limited function for us.

Disclosure to Website Service and Content Contractors

Certain content and services offered to you through our Website are served on Websites hosted and operated by a company other than ShopyBids ("Third Party Contractor Websites"). ShopyBids does not disclose your Personal Information to these Third Party Contractor Websites without your consent, but you should be aware that any information you disclose once you access these other sites is not subject to this Privacy Policy. ShopyBids does not endorse and is not responsible for the privacy practices of these Third Party Contractor Websites. You should review the privacy policy posted on the other site to understand how that Third Party Contractor Website collects and uses your Personal Information. ShopyBids makes an effort to make it obvious to you when you leave our Website and enter a Third Party Contractor Website, either by requiring you to click on a link or by notifying you on the site.

#### Disclosure of Aggregate Information

We may provide to third parties non-personal information about you that does not allow you to be identified or contacted and that is combined with the non-personal information of other users. For example, we might inform third parties regarding the number of users of our site and the activities they conduct while on our site. Depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge third parties for this Aggregate Information

#### Security Measures

Your Shopybids account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Shopybids will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Shopybids site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. While we strive to protect your personal information, We cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. As examples, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

#### Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam

Shopybids assures you that We will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms of Use. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and We will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by “web crawlers” or “web spiders” to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

#### General

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 7 days after they are initially posted on the site.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our servers. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your Personal Information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. Nevertheless, we promise that upon receiving your request, all Personal Information stored in the databases we actively use for research and daily business activities, and other readily searchable media, will be deleted.

Privacy as it applies to the Internet is a dynamic, rapidly developing area. In the future, we may make significant changes to our Privacy Policy affecting the use of the Personal Information we collect. We may also make non-significant changes to our Privacy Policy that generally will not affect our use of your Personal Information and we generally will not notify you of these non-significant changes. You should check this posted Privacy Policy for any non-significant changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the site immediately.

This site and the servers that make this site available are located in the United States. By using this site you agree to the transfer, collection, processing and use of data by this site as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not and will not apply in the event of ShopyBids's bankruptcy, dissolution, sale, merger or other similar corporate event.
